The past is a presence
Oracle is a horror film directed by Daniel di Grado.
A young woman accepts a job on a property with a traumatic history.
Upon her arrival, she soon realizes that the nightmares of her
childhood are connected to the evil in the house.
Shay, played by Ryan Destiny.
Kate, played by Heather Graham.
Jasmine, played by Ariel Martin.
Patrick, played by Samuel Isaiah Hunter.
Andrew, played by Nicholas Crovetti.
Chase, played by Cameron Crovetti.
Oracle is a 2023 American horror thriller film directed by Daniel Di
Grado from a screenplay by Michael Ross and Corey Harrell.
The film stars Ryan Destiny, Ariel Martin, and Heather Graham.
It was released on Max on October 1, 2023.
The tone is dark.